https://www.wes-tex.com/privacy_policy.html

Shopping Cart 00WelcomeGuest CustomerMy Account Home
Products Print Products4 Color DigitalBusiness Cards - DigitalBusiness Cards - Digital + FoilVinyl BannersWhite InkMagnetic Business Cards - Digital130C Premium - DigitalLetterhead - DigitalBookmarks - DigitalRack Cards - DigitalBrochures - DigitalFlyers - DigitalPosters - DigitalPostcards - DigitalHang Tags - DigitalTrading Cards - DigitalNotepads - DigitalMagnets - DigitalSimulated (Sim) Spot Ink & FoilFoil Exclusive Business CardsBusiness Cards - Sim SpotBusiness Cards - Sim Spot + FoilFoldover Business Cards - Sim SpotLetterhead - Sim SpotEnvelopes - Sim SpotLetterhead - Sim Spot + FoilEnvelopes - Sim Spot + FoilStationery - Blank StockSpot Ink & FoilAnnouncements with EnvelopesNotepads - SpotNCR Form - SpotNCR Wrap Around - Spot4 Color OffsetBusiness Cards - OffsetSilk Business Cards - OffsetFoldover Business Cards - OffsetLetterhead - OffsetEnvelopes - OffsetBookmarks - OffsetRack Cards - OffsetBrochures - OffsetFlyers - OffsetClub Flyers - OffsetPosters - OffsetPostcards - OffsetSilk Postcards - OffsetDoor Hangers - OffsetTable Tents - OffsetGreeting Cards - OffsetHoliday Cards - OffsetSilk Holiday Cards - OffsetSilk Greeting Cards - OffsetNotepads - OffsetPocket Folders - OffsetNCR Form - OffsetNCR Wrap Around - OffsetView All Promo ProductsWriting InstrumentsStic PensCombo PensClick PensTotes & BagsPaper BagsPlastic BagsView All Sample KitsSamplesFull Sample KitMini Sample PackMost PopularGold Foil Business CardsSilver Foil Business CardsSpot UV Business CardsView All
Contact Us
Downloads
Login / Register
* Email ID * Password LoginForgot password?New User ?Register Get a Quote
Print Products 4 Color Digital Business Cards - Digital Business Cards - Digital + Foil Vinyl Banners White Ink Magnetic Business Cards - Digital 130C Premium - Digital Letterhead - Digital Bookmarks - Digital Rack Cards - Digital Brochures - Digital Flyers - Digital Posters - Digital Postcards - Digital Hang Tags - Digital Trading Cards - Digital Notepads - Digital Magnets - DigitalSimulated (Sim) Spot Ink & Foil Foil Exclusive Business Cards Business Cards - Sim Spot Business Cards - Sim Spot + Foil Foldover Business Cards - Sim Spot Letterhead - Sim Spot Envelopes - Sim Spot Letterhead - Sim Spot + Foil Envelopes - Sim Spot + Foil Stationery - Blank StockSpot Ink & Foil Announcements with Envelopes Notepads - Spot NCR Form - Spot NCR Wrap Around - Spot4 Color Offset Business Cards - Offset Silk Business Cards - Offset Foldover Business Cards - Offset Letterhead - Offset Envelopes - Offset Bookmarks - Offset Rack Cards - Offset Brochures - Offset Flyers - Offset Club Flyers - Offset Posters - Offset Postcards - Offset Silk Postcards - Offset Door Hangers - Offset Table Tents - Offset Greeting Cards - Offset Holiday Cards - Offset Silk Holiday Cards - Offset Silk Greeting Cards - Offset Notepads - Offset Pocket Folders - Offset NCR Form - Offset NCR Wrap Around - Offset
Promo Products Writing Instruments Stic Pens Combo Pens Click PensTotes & Bags Paper Bags Plastic Bags
Sample Kits Samples Full Sample Kit Mini Sample Pack Top ProductsMost Popular Gold Foil Business Cards Silver Foil Business Cards Spot UV Business CardsPrivacy PolicyHomePrivacy PolicyWest Texas Printing Company ("Wes-Tex") is committed to maintaining the privacy and security of personal information received from all customers of Wes-Tex. In connection with the providing of requested goods and services to you, Wes-Tex received information about you and/or your company. This information may have included one or more e-mail addresses.At the time such information was delivered, you were informed that Wes-Tex could use such information to allow Wes-Tex to have future communication with you, and by providing such information, you granted permission for such use. However, such use is limited to internal use by Wes-Tex. Except with your consent, Wes-Tex will not sell, share or rent personal information to third parties. Notwithstanding the preceding, while Wes-Tex shall strive to protect the personal information of its customers, Wes-Tex will release personal information if required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary or appropriate.DATA OR INFORMATION COLLECTIONOur web sites, newsletters and, from time to time, certain other products and services, have features that automatically collect information from customers. Through this information gathering process, Wes-Tex is able to deliver content specific to customers' interests and to honor their preferences. This information also assists us in creating products and services that will serve the future needs of our customers.For example, we use "cookies," a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. If users reject the cookies, they may be limited in the use of some areas of our web site. By noting some of the pages the user visits on our web sites and via our e-mail newsletters, we can track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our sites and via e-mail newsletters.We may also send e-mails (including newsletters) for which you have registered (or otherwise agreed to receive). Cookies may be used in such e-mail messages to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising and how customers use our web sites and other products and services. We may combine demographics information supplied by a customer at registration with web site usage data to provide general profiles, in aggregate non-personally identifiable form, about our customers and their preferences in the content of the site and advertising. We may share this composite information (in non-personally identifiable form) with our advertisers and business affiliates to help them better understand our services.NOTIFICATION AND CHANGESIf we change our Privacy Policy Statement, we will post those changes on this page so our users are aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under which circumstances, if any, we disclose it. Users should check this policy frequently to keep abreast of any changes.For questions about this Privacy Policy Statement, contact:West Texas Printing Company
Attn: Sales and Solutions
2909 S. F. Austin Drive
P.O. Box 2303
Brownwood, Texas 76804
1-800-346-0515service@wes-tex.comSECURITYWes-Tex has security measures in place to help protect against the loss, misuse and/or unauthorized alteration of the information under our control. Wes-Tex helps protect personally identifiable information by utilizing both online and offline security methods, including firewalls, passwords and/or restricted physical access to the places where your information is stored. Our staff is trained to comply with our security procedures, and our security procedures are regularly reviewed and revised, if necessary.OTHER PROVISIONSAcceptance of Terms/Changes to Privacy Policy Statements -- Your continued receipt of the Wes-Tex e-mail newsletter and/or your continued use of the Wes-Tex web site indicates an acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy Statement. Wes-Tex reserves the right to update or amend this Privacy Policy Statement at any time.Disclaimer -- Wes-Tex provides information on many topics. Some of this information is created by Wes-Tex, and some of it is created by third parties. While our newsletter and web site strives to provide accurate expert advice, commentary and other information, Wes-Tex does not make any warranty regarding the accuracy, reliability or use of any information provided on this site or in the newsletter.Other -- In the event that Wes-Tex sells, assigns or transfers some or all of its business to a successor or acquirer, Wes-Tex may sell, assign or transfer all of your information, regardless of your opt status, to such successor or acquirer.Links to Other Sites -- The Wes-Tex web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that Wes-Tex does not exercise control over the information, products, services or policies of third party companies accessible through our site. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy policies of each and every third party site. This Privacy Policy Statement applies solely to the information collected by the Wes-Tex web site.Choice/Opt-out -- Wes-Tex users are given the opportunity to "opt-out" of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site. Wes-Tex will only communicate with you according to your instructions. If you have any questions relating to opting-out, please contact us at service@wes-tex.com.
